

## Huỳnh Phi Khanh

Software Developer



DOB: 18/9/1999

## **OBJECTIVE**

Procient junior software engineer with 2 years of experience in designing and implementing software applications. Utilize React, Python, AWS to write scalable appsfor thousands of users.

Aiming to work with a fast growing company with a focus on Web / Software Development and Al. I have had exposure to OpenAl,

DeepSeek, AWS.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **TMA Solutions**

May 2023 - Aug 2024

#### Otto International

May 2022 - Nov 2022

#### DEVELOPER

Responsible for developing and implementing software solutions for network devices.

- Stack: Python, CI/CD, Git, Linux, Bash, Surfshark, FTP.
- Implemented Python scripts to automate network switch configurations, reducing manual efforts by 50%.
- Part of the automation development team. Interacted with clients from the US and India.
- Solid understanding of networking concepts, including TCP/IP, VLANs, and SNMP.

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN**

Assisted in the design and development of an apparel web application.

- Stack: Groovy Grails, Java, AWS, Git, Github, Spring Framework, SQL, PostgreSQL, Jira.
- Contributed to the development of a new feature that increased efficiency by 20% and customer satisfaction by 15%.
- Part of the Product Lifecycle Management team. Utilized Agile and Scrum.
- Optimized existing codebase, resulting in a 10% reduction in processing time.
- Consistently met project deadlines and received a commendation for dedication and focus.

#### **PROJECT**

#### Mekong

Jun 2024 - Oct 2024

E-Commerce Web Application

#### **DEVELOPER**

Responsible for designing, implementing and deploying a MERN web application from scratch. Mobile friendly, has payment features and user features.

MONGODB, EXPRESS, REACT, REDUX, NODE, JWT, GIT, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, VSCODE, DOCKER.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Computer Science Bachelor of Science** 

2017 - 2021: California State University East Bay

RELEVANT COURSES: WEB DEVELOPMENT, SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT, MACHINE LEARNING, COMPUTER SECURITY

Dean's List of 2021 and 2022

### **SKILLS**

Languages: Python, C++, React/Redux, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

DBRM: MongoDB, SQL, PostgreSQL, Google BigQuery

Tools: Git, Github, OpenAl, Docker, Jenkins

Libraries: JWT, Pandas, React TLK, Matplotlib, Scikit Learn

Fluent in English and Vietnamese

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **REFERENCES**

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

May 2024

Google Data Analytics Professional. https://coursera.org/share/6c66695e Github:

https://github.com/kaynhelga9

Strengths: Team player, adaptable, quick to learn, collaborative, passionate towards anything tech.

Other hobbies: music, aviary.